

Sjors Sparreboom

4 17 November 1990

mail@sjorssparreboom.nl



ttp://sjorssparreboom.nl



(+31) 641 77 44 22



P EEC1 9F10 7DD3 801B D3ED 4231 9088 4F4B 36BE BC5B



http://github.com/SirJls

Sjors Sparreboom

Student / Software Engineer

About me

Graduate computer science student with a professional background in system management and cryptography. Having worked on several international peacekeeping missions and trainings covering the roles: Communication Information Specialist and Royal Marine. Obtaining the following attributes:

Disciplined: This was demonstrated in the previous position as Royal Marine by making sure real time communication was possible under any circumstances on any continent.

Energetic: Aiming to use my energetic personality to contribute to a better working environment, believing that a combination of positive energy and a positive mindset make for a better working environment.

Personal Growth: Taking time for personal growth, believing that stagnation means decline. This was demonstrated by going back to school after seven years in a pursuit of knowledge. Also developing a keen interest in mathematics and functional programming in my spare time.

Education

2014 - Current, Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences Bachelor in Computer Science

2010 - 2011, Marine Trainings Center

Marine Advanced Signaller / Communication and Information Specialist

2009 - 2010, Marine Trainings Center

Marine First Class



Experience

May 2016 - 2017, Trainee Software Engineer, Ivaldi

Trainee Software Engineer, was responsible for maintaining, extending and building back-end solutions for modern web-applications, mostly in Ruby.

- Added e-mail template functionality to BRIMIR a open source ticket manager, introducing the option for automatic replies.
- · Added a calendar extension to BRIMIR, which let's you decide when to receive e-mails.
- Added Captcha authentication to BRIMIR, to prevent bots from creating multiple tickets.
- · Added regular expression parser for the e-mail templates to BRIMIR, allowing variables inside brackets to be automatically replaced by known content.
- Added read/unread status to tickets.
- Extended e-mail filter.
- Upgraded BRIMIR to Ruby On Rails 5.
- Fixed several bugs in BRIMIR.
- Added multi-language support to the skillpower website.

May 2009 - 2014, Royal Marine, Royal Netherlands Navy

Participated in international peacekeeping operations. Deployable all over the world in forty-eight hours. To successfully complete these missions skills obtained from mandatory trainings in the most varied circumstances and a physical and mental stability were demanded.

- Trained to operate in any environment, under any condition and circumstances.
- Took part in several anti-piracy operations in the Gulf of Aden and Somalia.
- Took part in different trainings all around the globe.
- Responsible real time commutation with HQ under any circumstances and in any continent.
- Responsible for encrypting and decrypting messages sent over safex, HF, VHF or TCP/IP.

Software Development Skills

Programming

 \circ C# \circ Shell \circ C \circ Haskell \circ F# \circ Ruby

Computer Software

Arch LinuxAndroidViMNETTmuxXMonad